Guide to the Erroll Garner Archive, 1942-2010 AIS.2015.09 AIS.2015.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio/Video Material, VI.
  - Sound Recordings, 1.
    - Reel-to-Reel Tapes
      Recordings feature Garner in the studio for Columbia, Atlantic, BMG, CBS, Gotham Recording, Polygram, Octave Records, Associated Recording Studios, Capitol, A&R, Blue Note, Mercury, RCA, etc. Notable albums include "Erroll Garner Plays Gershwin and Kern," "Dreamstreet," "That's My Kick," "Up In Erroll's Room," "Feeling Is Believing," "Magician," " A New Kind Of Garner," "Eleven," "Movie Favorites," (Japanese), "A New Kind Of Love" soundtrack, "A Night At The Movies," a recording in an Australian studio most likely done on tour, plus the live recording from the landmark "Concert By The Sea."
      Others include Garner live performances, compilation tapes of Garner compositions, solo piano sessions that have not been released, versions of "I Can't Get Started" and "Just Blues" (and others) with Garner on the harpsichord, plus a number of tapes entitled "noodling" where Garner is simply improvising. There is a 1956 session with Nat Pierce doing arrangements for the orchestra, original tunes, not full songs, sketches and rehearsals. Other well-known Garner songs include "Misty," including out-takes, "A Fine Romance," "Dreamstreet," "Dreamy," "Gaslight," etc.
      Television, radio and live concert performances include WHUR Howard University, The Tonight Show, Campus Concert, One World Performance, 1959 DJ convention, Dick Cavett Show, Pearl Bailey Show, 1956 Copenhagen radio performance, TV performance in Stockholm, Sweden, 1958 Detroit Masonic Temple, Arthur Godfrey Show, Godfrey Time, the Jackie Gleason Show, Balletap Show, the game show "Play Your Hunch," where he plays three songs and writes on impromptu; the 1963 Seattle World's Fair "One World" Concert, Village Gate, Amsterdam Concert (including a stereo master) and a 1958 Burlington, VT performance.
      Each reel holds between 1-20 songs, with most containing anywhere from three to 10. Production notes are often included. A database located in the the ASC Reading Room can be sesarched to identify reel information inlcuding inventory number, song, length, notes, format, band or solo, sound quality, etc. for most of the recordings where applicable.
      - Paris Television, 1966 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 09)
      - Paris Television, May 4, 1972 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 11)
      - Paris Television (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 12)
    - Cassettes
      There are approximately 1,981cassettes in the Erroll Garner archive. Content includes live and television performances, such as a 1964 Garner performance in Belgium; 1962 Holland performance, cassette reading "Four Original Tunes," Garner playing solo piano, 1952 Montreal performance, 1966 in NYC, 1964 "Jazz Nocturne," 1975 DC performance, 1940's Concerts, 1963 European concerts, Steve Allen Show, BBC, 1950 Woody Herman program, 1975 Birthday Party, 1958 Sy Johnson "For Erroll" Tribute, 1972 All-Stars with Coleman Hawkins and Jimmy Heath; Phil Schap, "Jazz Sundae," 1974 Tonight Show; Gary Giddins Show, 1972 Australia; 1948 With John Collins & Slam Stewart in Paris 1948; a tape marked "Erroll's Last Show," February 21, 1975 at Mr. Kelly's Tonight Show with June 1972 Tonight Show appearance with Flip Wilson subbing for Carson; studio performances, Garner bantering with band, solo work, numerous original compositions and several versions of "Misty."
      Garner interviews include the Arthur Godfrey Show, NPR "Morning Edition; an interview on Cape Cod, NPR Jazz Profile, 1966 Garner interview with George Shearing and Steve Allen; a 1966 "The Joy of A Genius" NPR Jazz Profile on Garner; etc.
      Also, numerous interviews regarding Garner's music and legacy with Martha Glaser are represented. Interviews with Art Blakey, George Avakian, Joe Turner, Red Callendar Billy Taylor, Carl McVicker, Slam Stewart, Teddy Wilson and Illinois Jacquet among other are included. A January 7, 1977 recording of Garner's funeral service, a 1988 Ron Della Chiesa WGBH tribute, and 1999 "A Portrait of Erroll Garner" program from the Netherlands can also be found among the cassettes.
      It appears that there is some content overlap with the acetates and tapes. Therefore, there is a lot of original material comprising interviews with Garner, Glaser or other celebrities talking about Garner, show performances, solo performances, and studio work.
    - Acetates, Discs, Test Pressings and Promotional Records
      Contains approximately 652 discs including items composted of aluminum, acetate (lacquer), and vinyl. Sizes vary from 7-inches to 16-inches. Among the disc recordings are full albums, test pressings, commercial recordings, live recordings, promotional recordings, reference stampers, 16"" Muzak discs likely containing Garner compositions. Most discs have been digitized. Many discs are housed in their original sleeves, some containing handwritten annotations likely written by the engineer or producer. Condition ranges from fair to excellent. Discs that are believed to have been part of Garner's personal colleciton exhibit cracks, scratches, and chips. Also included is the 2016 release two-album set Ready Take One which contains previously unreleased tracks.
  - Moving Images, 2.
    This series contains concert and television performances featuring Erroll Garner with his trio, solo, and other performers and notable personalities on both 16mm film and videocassette. Performances include appearances on The Ed Sullivan Show, The Tonight Show, The Gary Moore Show, BBC's Jazz 625, Jazzland, among others. Some videocassettes included in this series serve as documentation as to the use of Garner compositions in feature films, television shows, and advertising.
    Moving image media in 16mm film, videocassette, and digital formats can be viewed onsite in the ASC Reading Room.
    - Motion Picture Film
      - CBS Television Broadcast, March 26, 1961 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 01)
      - Television Broadcast, Swedish TV, 1970 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 02)
      - Erroll Garner in Performance, Swedish TV, August 26, 1980 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 03)
      - American Musical Theatre, July 5, 1977 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 04)
      - Montreaux Jazz Festival, May 24, 1967 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 05)
      - Amerian Musical Theater, February 13, 1965 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 06)
      - Laclede Symphony (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 07)
        The item is not dated; however, it is possible that it could be from March 1955 when Garner performed on the Laclede Symphony Hour program on KSD - TV while the St. Louis Symphony was on tour. He was the first jazz artist to be featured on the classical music program.
      - The Gary Moore Show, April 14, 1964 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 10)
      - The Perry Como Show, January 30, 1963 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 17)
      - Unknown French Television Show, ca. 1960s (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 13)
      - 7th Annual Pittsburgh United Fund--Edited Clips, September 30, 1962 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 18)
      - 7th Annual Pittsburgh United Fund--Longer Version, September 30, 1962 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 19)
      - The Bell Telephone Hour, June 16, 1964 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 20)
      - The Tonight Show, N.D. (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 21)
      - The Tonight Show, October 29, 1962 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 22)
      - The Ed Sullivan Show, ca. 1964-1965 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 23)
      - The Bell Telephone Hour, ca. 1964-1965 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 24)
      - TheTonight Show, November 19, 1973 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 25)
      - The Tonight Show, November 1, 1973 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 26)
      - The Tonight Show, October 29, 1962 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 27)
      - The Ed Sullivan Show, ca. 1961 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 28)
      - The Ed Sullivan Show, ca. 1961 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 29)
      - The Ed Sullivan Show, ca. 1961 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 30)
      - The Tonight Show, ca. 1973 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 31)
      - Tribute performance clips never before seen created for Newport Jazz Festival at Town Hall, April 1, 1983 (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 04 43)
      - Unknown (Oversize 55, Reel EGV 05 15)
    - Videocassettes
      - Hitachi Commercial, April 1, 1982 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 02)
      - Concert Recordings, London and Copenhagen, 1964,1970 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 03)
      - The Genius of Soul, 1991 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 04)
      - Jazzland, May 29, 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 05)
      - Documentary, 1998 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 07)
      - Documentary, 1998 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 08)
      - KCH clips, ca. 1970- 1977 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 09)
      - Jazzland- with timecode, May 29, 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 10)
      - Jazzland, May 29, 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 11)
      - Jazz Dance (1954) & After Hours (1961), 1954, 1961 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 12)
      - Jazzland, May 29, 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 13)
      - Jazz 625 Reel 1, February 20, 1965 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 14)
      - The Steve Allen Show, May 16, 1960 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 16)
      - Jazz 625 Reel 2, October 21, 1964 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 17)
        The tape is dated 1964, but Garner performed on the show in 1965.
      - Festival- Jazz Piano, 1973 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 19)
      - Jazz 625 II, October 24, 1964 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 20)
      - Nightline withTed Koppel, August 8, 1989 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 21)
      - The Erroll Garner Documentary Project, No One Can Hear You Read (4 tapes), 1997 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 22)
      - The Oprah Winfrey Show, N.D. (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 23)
      - Erroll Garner in Europe, ca. 1963-1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 24)
      - Vintage Jazz Collection--Jazz 625 (Labelled in Japanese), October 22, 1964 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 25)
      - The Tonight Show-- Final Show (Music Montage), May 22, 1992 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 26)
      - Concert Recording--Amsterdam, November 7, 1964 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 27)
      - Unknown, May 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 28)
      - Great Performances: Miles Ahead, 1986 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 29)
      - Jazz Memories, May 29, 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 30)
        Program contains "Misty," "Something." "Shadow of your Smile," and clips from from Jazz 625 from Studio 13,
      - Like It Is, Hosted by Gil Noble, ca. 1977-1987 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 31)
      - Jazz Concert Recordings London (1964),Copenhagen (1970), 1964-1970; Duplicate of EGV-01-03 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 01 33)
      - Evening at the Pops, July 19, 1978 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 01)
      - Dress Rehearsal, July 13, 1981 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 02)
      - Erroll Garner in Copenhagen, May 27, 1968 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 03)
      - Unknown (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 04)
      - Unknown, Februray 22, 1983 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 05)
      - The Bell Telephone Hour, June 14, 1964 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 06)
      - The Mike Douglas Show, ca. 1963-1970 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 07)
        Collection of mulitple Erroll Garner appearances.
      - The Ed Sullivan Show, 1960-1963 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 08)
        Collection of Erroll Garner appearances dated 10/23/1960; 2/5/1961; 3/26/1961; 4/21/1963.
      - Holland (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 09)
      - Jazz 625 Reels 1 and 2, Tape 1 of 2, Feburary 20, 1965 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 10)
      - Jazz/Beat with Erroll Garner, October 16, 1970 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 11)
      - Jazz 625 Reels 1 and 2, Tape 2 of 2, February 20, 1965 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 12)
      - Just Jazz: Erroll Garner, November 14, 1986 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 02 13)
      - The Tonight Show, November 19, 1973 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 01)
      - Just Jazz: Erroll Garner, November 14, 1986 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 03)
      - 1977 Memorial, January 16, 1977 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 02)
      - Unknown Production from French Television (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 04)
      - Unknown, August 26, 1983 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 05)
      - Rose D'Or/Montreux, 1966; PAL/Mono/B&W/10"-- wrong format- possible dupe of 03-13 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 08)
      - The Tonight Show, October 18, 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 09)
      - The Tonight Show, December 18, 1974 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 10)
      - The Today Show, Janaury 7, 1977 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 11)
      - The Tonight Show, May 28, 1973 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 12)
      - 18th Contest for the "Golden Rose of Montreux": Rose D'Or, 1966 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 13)
      - CBS News Sunday Morning, September 12, 1993; Beta (Oversize 55, Video EGV 03 14)
      - Erroll Garner in Performance (Oversize 55, Disc EGV 03 15)
      - Unknown Television Broadcast, January 28, 1993 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 01)
      - Unknown Concert Recording, 13/WNET, January 1, 1991 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 02)
      - Unknown BBC Television Broadcast, October 31, 1964 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 03)
      - Unknown Concert Recording (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 04)
      - Unknown BBC Television Broadcast (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 05)
      - Unknown (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 06)
      - Unknown BBC Program (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 07)
      - Unknown Concert Recording, ca. 1959-1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 08)
      - Uknown BBC Program (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 09)
      - Unknown (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 10)
      - Unknown, May 1, 1972 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 11)
      - Unknown (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 12)
      - Montreaux Jazz Festival, 1966 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 13)
      - CBS Sunday Morning, September 12, 1993 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 14)
      - A&E Television Broadcast, May 28, 1998 (Oversize 55, Video EGV 05 14)
  - Gear, etc., 3.
    This subseries contains miscellaneous cables, microphones, etc.
- Memorabilia, 1946-2006; VII.
  The Memorabilia series includes planners, books, scripts, awards, proclamations, business cards, postcards, stamps, passports, ID and membership cards, artwork by and of Garner, clothing, jewelry, keys, cufflinks, rings, watches and miscellaneous items.
  - Artwork, 1946-1990; 1.
    The Artwork subseries includes prints and illustrations of Garner by various artists. The subseries also includes artwork of other subjects owned by Garner, as well as sketches drawn by Garner himself.
    - Garner sketch from London Sunday Mirror (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Garner face sketch (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Garner sketch MGM Records (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - He's Here! He's Gone! He's Garner! album sleve (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - New Kind of Love Illustration (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Garner drawing from portrait by Rheinhold W. Timm, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - News Pool Sketch (2) (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Unicover Corporation (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Sketches by Garner (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Garner Drawing by Bruni Sablan, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Sketches from watercolors by Daniel Appelbaum (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Sketches by Desow (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Matted prints (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Garner Trio Print and Sketch (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Sketches of Garner unknown artists (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Awards, 1956-1996; 2.
    The Awards subseries includes award plaques and certificates received by Garner during his career from music organizations within the United States and around the world. The subseries also includes awards recognizing the enduring popularity of Garner's music from The American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP), and the National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences (NARAS).
    - ASCAP Certificate of Membership for Octave Music Corp, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Melhor Solista Internacional De (Portuguese, Gold Disc Emblem In Envelope, 6 x 8), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Downbeat Award, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Downbeat Award, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Downbeat Award- First Place Piano 1, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Downbeat Award- First Place Piano 2, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Hot Club de France-Grand Prix du Disque de Jazz certificate, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Downbeat Award, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Phi Alpha Jazz Musician of the Year, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Philips Electrical Reception, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Playboy All Star Certificate, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Bound copy of The Saturday Evening Post, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Up in Erroll's Room Grammy Nomination Plaque, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Sindicato Argentino de Musicos Certificate (Spanish), 1970 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Clube Dos Amigos Do Jazz De Sao Paulo Award (Portuguese), 1970 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Pride of Pennsylvania Award, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - ASCAP Award to Octave Music Publishing Corp. for Misty- Outstanding Country Song, October 15, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - ASCAP Award to Octave Music Publishing Corp. for Misty- Outstanding Country Song, October 14, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - ASCAP Award to Octave Music Publishing Corp. for Misty- Outstanding Country Song, [ON EXHIBIT], October 14, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - ASCAP Honors Octave Music Publishing Corp. for "Misty" - Among the Most Performed ASCAP Standards October 1, 1973-September 30, 1983, May 3, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - ASCAP Honors Erroll Garner for "Misty" - Among the Most Performed ASCAP Standards October 1, 1973-September 30, 1983 [ON EXHIBIT], May 3, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - ASCAP Honors Erroll Garner for "Misty" - Among the Most Performed ASCAP Standards October 1 1974-September 30, 1984, May 28, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - ASCAP Honors Erroll Garner for "Misty" - Among the Most Performed ASCAP Standards October 1, 1975-September 30, 1985, May 28, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - ASCAP Honors Octave Music Publishing Corp. for "Misty" - Among the Most Performed ASCAP Standards October 1 1975-September 30, 1985, May 28, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Grammy Awards Program, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - NARAS Hall of Fame Entry Form, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Books and TV Scripts, 1959-2006; 3.
    The Books and TV Scripts subseries includes books on jazz that mention Garner, books on other subjects owned by Garner, and original scripts from Garner's television appearances throughout his career.
    - American Popular Songs: Six Decades of Songwriters and Singers, selected by James R. Morris, J.R. Taylor, and Dwight Blocker Bowers, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Between You and Me- Pearl Bailey, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - The Book of Jazz: A Guide to the Entire Field - Leonard Feather, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Detroit Yellow Pages phonebook [ON EXHIBIT] (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Dictionary of Music - Theodore Karp, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Erroll Garner: Leben Und Kunst Eines Genialen Pianisten - Ernst Burger (Germany), 2006 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Esquire's 1947 Jazz Book (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Exits and Entrances, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Flip, NBC TV Script [ON EXHIBIT], 1971 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - The Gary Moore Show, CBS TV Script [ON EXHIBIT], 1959 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - The Golden Age of Jazz - William P. Gottlieb, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - His Way: The Unauthorized Autobiography of Frank Sinatra - Kitty Kelley, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Living with Jazz - Dan Morgenstern, ed. by Sheldon Meyer, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - The Oxford Companion to Jazz, ed. by Bill Kirchner, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Perry Como's Kraft Music Hall, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Talking to Myself - Pearl Bailey, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - War Is No Damn Good!- Robert Osborn, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - The World of Count Basie - Stanley Dance, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Cards, 1973-1981; 4.
    The Cards subseries consists of Garner's personal cards, including business cards, identification cards, passports, membership cards, medical cards, petty cash vouchers, and a social security card.
    - Garner Business Cards (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Identification Cards and Passports (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Medical Cards (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Membership Cards (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Personal Thank You Card, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Petty Cash Vouchers (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Social Security Card (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Contacts, 5.
    The Contacts subseries includes three address books and address cards containing Garner's business, personal, and celebrity contacts.
    - Address Book (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Address Book (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Address Book (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Address Cards A-L (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Address Cards M-Z (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Business Cards (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Memoriam, 6.
    The Memoriam subseries includes proclamations and resolutions from government and music organizations honoring Garner and recognizing his contributions to music.
    - California Legislature Memorial Resolution, February 10, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 14-17)
    - New York Public Library Schomburg Center Letter, May 12, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - State of Pennsylvania Recognition, June 6, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Erroll Garner Day Proclamation, June 15, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - ASCAP Pied Piper Award Press Release and Correspondence, September 22, 1977- November 12, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Linton Garner Thanks... (Box 59, Disc 1)
      Includes memorable studio recordings and the heartfelt tribute concert to his brother Erroll, "I Never said Goodbye." Produced by Don Fraser. Recorded CBC Radio - July 2, 1993; June 24, 2002, Carltone Studio - November 5, 2004
  - Publicity, 7.
    The Publicity subseries includes promotional materials used by Garner during his career, and commemorative postage stamps and postcards honoring Garner and his musical legacy.
    - Legends of American Jazz Postage Stamps (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Postcards, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Publicity Impression Cards (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Publicity Packet (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 8.
    - Four Leaf Clover (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Just Jazz PBS Box (Box 60, Item 1)
    - Back Cover of Unknown Album (Box 60, Item 2)
    - Shaving Kit Bag (Box 60, Item 3)
    - Wooden Stamp (Box 60, Item 4)
    - Embossers (Box 60, Item 5-9)
    - Brown Wallet (Box 60, Item 10)
    - Wood Block (Box 60, Item 11)
    - Music Roll with High Octane (Box 60, Item 12)
    - Music Roll with Misty, Young Love, High Octane (Box 60, Item 13)
    - Galileoscope with Case (Box 60, Item 14)
  - Clothing, 9.
    The Clothing subseries includes eleven custom-made dress shirts worn by Garner, as well as a tie worn by Garner in its original box.
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Green (Box 61, Item 1)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Green (Box 61, Item 2)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Orange (Box 61, Item 3)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Green (Box 61, Item 4)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Green (Box 61, Item 5)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Green (Box 61, Item 6)
    - Dress Shirt, Littler, Light Yellow (Box 61, Item 7)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Green (Box 61, Item 8)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Yellow (Box 61, Item 9)
    - Dress Shirt, Murray Lee, White (Box 61, Item 10)
    - Dress Shirt, Fred Sanders, Blue (Box 61, Item 11)
    - Tiecrafters Tie in Box (Box 61, Item 12)
  - Jewelry, 10.
    The Jewelry subseries includes coins, keychains, pocket watches, earrings, money pins, keys, cigarette lighters, rings, tie bands, money clips, cuff links, and other personal items.
    - American Lincoln Memorial Cents (4) (Box 62, Item 1)
    - American Lincoln Wheat Cents (4) (Box 62, Item 2)
    - French Coins (3) (Box 62, Item 3)
    - Italian Coins (2) (Box 62, Item 4)
    - West German Coin (1) (Box 62, Item 5)
    - British Halfpenny (1) (Box 62, Item 6)